http://www.organicgardeninfo.com/privacy-policy.html

Your Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy Information For OrganicGardenInfo
It's important that you read OrganicGardenInfo.com's Privacy
Policy information, before using this web site.
We recognize that your privacy is important. This document
outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when
you use OrganicGardenInfo.com, as well as some of the steps we take to
safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed
decision about sharing personal information with us.
OrganicGardenInfo.com strives to maintain the highest
standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations.
Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting our customers', consumers' and
online visitors' privacy on our website.
Personal Information
OrganicGardenInfo.com collects personally identifiable information from
the visitors to our website only on a voluntary basis. Personal
information collected on a voluntary basis may include name, postal
address, email address, company name and telephone number.
This information is collected if you request information from
us, participate in a contest or sweepstakes, and sign up to join our
email list or request some other service or information from us. The
information collected is internally reviewed, used to improve the
content of our website, notify our visitors of updates, and respond to
visitor inquiries.
Once information is reviewed, it is discarded or stored in our
files. If we make material changes in the collection of personally
identifiable information we will inform you by placing a notice on our
site. Personal information received from any visitor will be used only
for internal purposes and will not be sold or provided to third parties.
Use of Cookies and Web Beacons
We may use cookies to help you personalize your online experience.
Cookies are identifiers that are transferred to your computer's hard
drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your
browser. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you
have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize the
sites pages, or register with any of our site's services, a cookie
enables OrganicGardenInfo.com to recall your specific information on
subsequent visits.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying
your Web browser; however, if you choose to decline cookies, you may
not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the site.
A web beacon is a transparent image file used to monitor your
journey around a single website or collection of sites. They are also
referred to as web bugs and are commonly used by sites that hire
third-party services to monitor traffic. They may be used in
association with cookies to understand how visitors interact with the
pages and content on the pages of a web site.
We may serve third party advertisements that use cookies and
web beacons in the course of ads being served on our web site to
ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. No personally
identifiable information you give us is provided to them for cookie or
web beacon use, so they cannot personally identify you with that
information on our web site.
Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies or notify you
when a cookie is being sent. Privacy software can be used to override
web beacons. Taking either of these actions shouldn't cause a problem
with our site, should you so choose.
Children's Online Privacy Protection Act
This website is directed to adults; it is not directed to children
under the age of 13. We operate our site in compliance with the
Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, and will not knowingly
collect or use personal information from anyone under 13 years of age.
Non-Personal Information
In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not
personally identifiable. We use this information, which does not
identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site,
to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic
information about our user base as a whole. The information collected
is used solely for internal review and not shared with other
organizations for commercial purposes.
Release of Information
If OrganicGardenInfo.com is sold, the information we have obtained from
you through your voluntary participation in our site may transfer to
the new owner as a part of the sale in order that the service being
provided to you may continue. In that event, you will receive notice
through our website of that change in control and practices, and we
will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honors any
opt-out requests you might make of us.
How You Can Correct or Remove Information
We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment
to protect your personal information. If you have submitted personal
information through our website and would like that information deleted
from our records or would like to update or correct that information,
please click on this link and/or use our Contact Us page.
Updates and Effective Date
OrganicGardenInfo.com reserves the right to make changes in this
privacy policy. If there is a material change in our privacy policy
practices, we will indicate on our site that our privacy practices have
changed and provide a link to the new privacy policy. We encourage you
to periodically review this privacy policy so that you will know what
information we collect and how we use it.
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you
visit our website. These companies may use information (not including
your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your
visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements
about goods and services of interest to you.
ADDRESS Your Internet Protocol ("IP") address is usually
associated with the place from which you enter the Internet, like your
Internet Service Provider, your company or your university. We may use
your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, gather broad
demographic information, and administer our website.
Kids And Parents
Although there is not - nor ever will be - anything
intentionally offensive on my website, it is not intended for use by
children, especially those under age 13. No one under age 13 is allowed
to provide any personal information. Minors between the ages of 13 and
17 must get the permission of their parent(s) or legal guardian(s)
before making purchases or asking questions on this site.
If your children disclose information about themselves in
publicly accessible areas of the Website, they may get unsolicited
messages from other parties. Accordingly, you should tell them not to
do so. If you're worried about your children's activities or their
privacy on our site, we encourage you to e-mail our Privacy Policy
Coordinator thru our "Contact Me" page.If you have other concerns or
questions about any aspect of this policy, you may also e-mail me at my
"Contact Me" section of the website.. I welcome your questions and
feedback.
Additional Note: Google Adsense
If you elect to click on an ad generated by Google AdSense,
make note of their policies as follows:
Google Advertising Cookie and Privacy Policies
What is the DoubleClick DART cookie?
The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads
served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. When
users visit an AdSense publisher's website and either view or click on
an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. The data
gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers
better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web.
Google and the DoubleClick DART cookie:
* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads
on your site. * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads
to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the
Internet. * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting
the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
Because publisher sites and laws across countries vary, we're
unable to suggest specific privacy policy language. However, you may
wish to review resources such as the Network Advertising Initiative, or
NAI, which suggests the following language for data collection of
non-personally identifying information:
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you
visit our website. These companies may use information (not including
your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your
visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements
about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more
information about this practice and to know your choices about not
having this information used by these companies, click here.
You can find additional information in Appendix A of the NAI
Self-Regulatory principles for publishers (PDF). Please note that the
NAI may change this sample language at any time.
Read Google's policy on Adsense
If you would like more information about this practice and to
know your choices about not having this information used by these
companies...Click
Here
Agreeing to Terms
If you do not agree to OrganicGardenInfo.com
Privacy Policy as posted here on this website, please do not use this
site or any services offered by this site.
Your use of this site indicates acceptance of
this privacy policy.
Return from Privacy Policy to Home Page
Comments
Have your say about what you just read! Leave me a comment in the box
below.
[?]Subscribe To This Site
HomeBlogSoilGarden SoilCompostOrganic FertilizersVegetablesGrowing VegetablesGarden BedsVegetable IndexVegetable SeedsIntercroppingInsectsPest ControlInsect Pest FinderInsectipediaLunar GardeningMoon GardeningResourcesGardening ToolseStore ProductsWeb Search & NewsFree eBooksYour Garden StoriesKeep In TouchContact Us
Privacy
Policy
Copyright © OrganicGardenInfo.com All rights reserved.
